FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER · SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Ceará, Brazil - UTC-3

【 (+55) 85-99713-0901 | ■ dyegoaurelio@gmail.com | dyegoaurelio | dyegoaurelio

Skills

Front-end React - Next.js - Redux - React - Vite - HTML5 - CSS

Component Libraries Mui - Mantine - Styled Components - Bootstrap

DevOps Docker - Azure - GitHub Actions - Nginx

Back-end Flask - Django - FastApi - Express.js - PostgreSQL

About

I'm extremely passionate about programming, web development and Linux. I've worked with many full stack technologies, mostly using Typescript and Python. I'm a great problem solver and can work with agile environments.

I also like open source projects, so I contribute whenever I'm able to help projects I use.

Experience_

Mobills Ceará, Brazil

FRONTEND DEVELOPER Mar. 2021 - Dec. 2021

• Worked on many new features, refactors and bug fixes on Mobills web platform, using React, Redux and Redux Saga

Personalized Zendesk templates using Vanilla JS and CSS for Mobills Help Center

Pax Insurance Broker Ceará, Brazil

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Mar. 2021 - Present

- Developed a system to manage costumer's Health Insurance changes
- Creation of Power Bi panels for business presentations
- Developed a database to store all costumer's data
- Development of various systems in order to automate many company's internal processes using Python ans Pandas

Languages_

English Advanced **Portuguese** Native

Education

UFC(Federal University of Ceará)

Ceará, Brazil

Renewable Energy Engineering 2018 - Now

Dyego A. Costa · Résumé